glory to ukraine for those who do not understand
слава украине для тех кто не понимает
ukrainian at the end there will be messages in
украинский в конце будет сообщения на
russian
русском
favorite speech languages docs looking for channel 9 vin d
любимые спи вич языки docs ищет 9 канал
esel on us attack get fangs contr
вин дизель на нас атаку достать клыки
bution informative guilt against the russi
вклад информативную вину против
n federation and please bring
российской федерации и дуже прошу вас
the river you for russia you signi
притащите ривер ты за россию вы
g even often happened like this  stil
подписания даже часто бывало так еще
lyudyna subscribed and youtube plague with
людына подписывалась а youtube чуму
benefits and drink the search so the cent has
выгодами и пить поиску так и цент уже
even already come out and then even more sprats
даже вышла а потом еще чем больше кильки
signed more sprats from people
подписан больше кильки из людей ба да ба
signed and plus there 20500 teeming 200 not
подписан и плюс там 20500 кишат 200 не
signed and that the channels have up to 100,000
подписан и что у каналам до 100000
subscribers so youtube can show
подписчиков так то youtube можно покажет
with 100 thousand people signed and plus
с 100 тысячам людей подписанным и плюс
22 weave is not signed then someone else
22 сотки не подписан то кто-то еще
gives up a drink how will you batch it these
выпить пасует как вы буду это батчат эти
videos and bachil  come back on youtube
ролики так и и бачил вернись on youtube
gd recommends both him and the scientist signed
gd рекомендует и его и ученый подписан
so needed already came out for your contribution
так нужен уже вышла за ваш вклад
informative guilt korzh subscribe
информативный вину корж подписывайтесь
us kilogram min in office  Ise and the room and
нами килограмм мин в офисе и комнату и
you all kinds of binding so that Poland
ты все виды обовязково того чтобы польши
people read comments come in 30th
люди читают комментарии come in 30th
you can without alloy you us in the house mica and
можно без сплава ты нас в доме слюда и
denunciations you think the right speeches and
доносы ты думаешь правильные речи и
comments petr him and
комментарии петр ему и
paint the width of the mind also and is
покрасить по ширине виду еще и
documented so youtube bachek lyuda
документируется так youtube бачек люда
him but why  it was showing even
его но зачем его это был показываю еще
more king this be a weasel right at a time
больше кинг эту будь ласка прям за раз
vaccinations prescription for a
прививки предписание на
moment the channel and the subscriber is not subscribed yet
миг канал и подписчица еще не подписан
put a ton of hell
поставьте тонный черта
sign on the telegram in the office and don't
подпишите на телеграмме в офисе и не
forget the commentary you absolutely
забывайте комментура ты усе абсолютно
see you as if it is an education your
виду вы словно it is an education ваша
political position to floats  on a
политическая позиция к вплывает на
pinch of our speeder man so the most ki
пинчик наших спидер ман так самые ки
doubts to be in what he reads the
сомневается находиться в чем он читает
smoke of the face and the account of a lot of people
дым лица и счет дуже багато людей
to think like this and icons and
мыслить так и иконы и
establish themselves in their own words go kvn
утвердиться в своей идут слова квн
now for people who don’t understand
теперь для людей которые не понимают
ukrainian google who are watching us
украинские загуглите которые нас смотрят
with kazakhstan there brought down russia with russia
с казахстаном там сбил руси с россией
so the main part of my viewers is
так основная часть моих зрителей это
ukraine about 80 percent so russia up to
украина около 80 процентов так россия до
eight percent i still have stra  n
восьми процентов у меня еще есть стран
there kazakhstan belarus other countries of the
там казахстан беларусь другие страны
world
мира
your contribution is also very important subscribe
ваш вклад тоже очень важно подпишитесь
subscribe why because the more
подпишитесь почему потому что чем больше
subscribers the more other
подписанных тем больше других людей
unsubscribed people will also see this
неподписанных тоже будут видеть этот
video youtube watches the more
ролик youtube смотрит чем больше
subscribers the channel has the
подписчиков у канала тем еще большему
more people it shows the video
количеству людей он показывает видео
so if you sit there  in russia
поэтому если вы сидите там в россии
somewhere in irkutsk near moscow there is ulan ude
где-то иркутск подмосковье там улан-удэ
it’s nalchik it doesn’t matter you are afraid to go to the
это нальчик неважно вы боитесь выйти на
rally you understand that russia is the aggressor
митинг вы понимаете что россии агрессор
but you are afraid because a lot of people
но боитесь потому что очень много людей
around you think what is needed for this
вокруг вас думают что надо за эту
operation and so on so subscribe to
операцию и так дальше так подпишитесь на
this channel with this you will do  so that
этот канал этим вы сделаете так что
more Russian people will be
большему количеству людей россиян будет
shown my videos and some of them
показываться мои ролики и часть из них
will think, that is, your
будет задуматься то есть ваших
compatriots who will
соотечественников которые будут думать
already think correctly how you will become
уже правильно как вы будет ставать
more and you will not be outcasts in your
больше и вы не будете изгоями в своих
cities that you will be scared
городах что вам будет страшно с кем-то
to speak against someone there  you but because
там за говорить против вы а потому что
people who will understand that it is not
людей которые будут понимать что не
Ukraine that bombed the don for 8 years  Bass, not Ukraine,
украина 8 лет бомбила донбасс не украина
started the war in Donbass,
начала войну на донбассе
all all this fuss that it was not Ukraine that
всю всю всю эту суету что не украина
violated the Minsk agreements, we all
нарушала минские договоренности мы все
sort it out in fact, this is very, very important
разбираем по факту это очень-очень важно
because yours and the good sphere and yours and
потому что ваша и блага сфера и ваша и
television works to
телевидения работает на то чтобы
justify justify this Russian
оправдать оправдать вот эту российскую
aggression, so
агрессию поэтому
if  you are afraid there is something
если вы боитесь там что-то активные
active they are doing in russia subscribe to
действия делают в россии подпишитесь на
this it will be your drop at least in
этого это будет ваша капля хотя бы в
this fight comment on the video
этой борьбе комментируйте видео
comment on the video because youtube
комментируйте видео потому что youtube
will watch and people from russia
будет смотреть а люди из россии
comment on the video it means it is interesting to us
комментирует видео значит нам это
and more people from
интересно и большему количеству людей из
russia it will be  it showed
россии он будет это показывал
subscribe to my telegram channel also
подпишитесь на мой телеграм-канал также
these are small things that you
это маленькие такие вещи которыми вы
can help in this information
можете помочь в этой информационной
struggle so that your country, among other things,
борьбе чтобы ваша страна в том числе
becomes more civilized, it does not
стала более цивилизован она не
support the war, the murder of the neighboring
поддерживала войну убийство соседнего
people and in this country you feel
народа и в этой стране себя чувствовали
more comfortable, so subscribe right now
более комфортно поэтому прямо сейчас
if  not signed if
подпишитесь если не подписан если
signed check or signed and
подписаны проверьте или подписан и
because youtube sometimes drops your
потому что youtube бывает сбивает
subscription when you for some reason,
подписку при вы по каким то причинам
so do it right now and it
поэтому прямо сейчас это сделать и это
will be your small contribution to the
будет ваш небольшой вклад в
information war against this
информационную войну против вот этой
monstrous system that has seized
чудовищной системы которая захватила
power in the Russian Federation and
власть в российской федерации и хочет
wants to enslave other peoples,
хочет поработить другие народы
hold on
держимся